And welcome, to the beautiful studios of Valley Free Radio, located in a basement.
Anyway, we're going to show you today the basics of how to do old school, analog style broadcasting, and a very low tech, ancient style broadcasting studio.
So, let's take a look at what we've got here.
Of course, the heart of any studio is your broadcast board, so, we're going to talk about all that in a minute.
And most of the rest of what you see are different things that are going to be inputs to the board.
Got some CD players, we've got another mixing board that goes as one input to the, to the a, to the board.
We've got a couple cassette players, hi-tech.
And, we have a computer that we play MP3's to, and of course, the telephone.
And, we'll also see how to put callers on the air.
Other features of the station are, some very kicking monitors, microphones we'll be talking about, headphones you need when you're talking on the mike, and some turntables.
All here, at beautiful, Valley Free Radio.